pakadtrader.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. We recognize the importance of protecting your privacy and our policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers’ needs.

All personal information about you ("User") collected by PakAdTrader ("pakadtrader.com") is protected by this Privacy Policy.  
PakAdTrader will not sell rent or otherwise distribute User's personal information.

If User submit a website link, coupon and/or article ("listing") for review to pakadtrader.com, PakAdTrader may send User email in relation to the status of that listing (Status Emails). User agrees to receive Status Emails as a condition of submitting User listing. An example of a Status Email would be to tell User that User listing had been accepted into the PakAdTrader Website.  
Other emails may include updates to the Terms of Use, Link Submission, Article Submission, Coupon Submission, any and all Policy documents, this Privacy Policy and promotions offered by PakAdTrader.

 **What Information Do We Collect?**  
When you visit this web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

 **1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

 **Registration Information**  
When you register for any of our products, services or newsletters you will provide us information about yourself.

The only personally identifiable information about User ("PII") (e.g., User name, e-mail or physical address, or telephone number) that PakAdTrader receives is any PII User choose to include in the submission form if User submit a listing for consideration for inclusion in PakAdTrader. PakAdTrader will use such PII only in connection with the provision of PakAdTrader and for the purpose of evaluating volunteer editors, and do not use it for marketing purposes. PakAdTrader will not share your PII with any outside company, person or entity.

 **2\. Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and web server log files to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site.

 **How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**  
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing the products and services you requested, to process your payment, to monitor the use of the service, our marketing and promotional efforts and improve our content and service offerings, and customize our site’s content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personally identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law.

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at the link provided on the newsletter.

 **What Are Cookies?**  
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our site will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.

 **Usage of Cookies**  
When User use or access pakadtrader.com, PakAdTrader automatically receives and stores certain information ("cookies") from user browser, including user IP address; user browser type; access date and time; the referring Web site address; pakadtrader.com page User requested; and in the case of a search, the specific search terms requested. PakAdTrader uses this information for purposes of security, to learn more about how pakadtrader.com is used, and to improve the quality and usefulness of pakadtrader.com. PakAdTrader does NOT link any of this information with PII, and PakAdTrader will not share this information with any outside company, person or entity. PakAdTrader reserves the right to create a retention policy for PII and browser information for our business purposes, including the prevention of fraud and abuse of pakadtrader.com.

 **IP Addresses**  
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

 **Sharing and Selling Information**  
We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identifies a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.

 **How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**  
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by using the Contact form of this website.

 **What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?**  
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. We may also disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the Public.

 **What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Website to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on our Website, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

 **Your Consent**  
By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

 **Our Commitment To Data Security**  
Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your Country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out**  
This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.

 **Surveys and Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

 **A Special Note About Children**  
Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.

 **Acquisition or Changes in Ownership**  
In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

 **Policy Modifications**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

Any questions relating to our Privacy Policy should be directed to our Privacy section using our [Contact form](http://www.pakadtrader.com/contact.php).
